It will be managed by a partner under it.
For this purpose, in the financial year 2019,
major projects will be
launched under the Public Private Partnership (PPP) mode. Under this, Rs. 12,122 crore will be allocated for fuel.
Under this, Rs. 2,000 crore will be
allocated for the promotion of
merchant shipping in India. A scheme will be launched to promote merchant shipping in India, under
which
Indian shipping companies will be provided with subsidies in global tenders issued by ministries and CPOs.
For this, an
amount of Rs. 1,624 crore will be made available in the next five years. Apart from increasing the share of Indian companies
in the global setting, such efforts will also provide
better training and employment opportunities to Indian citizens.
India has enacted the Recycling of Waste Act
2019, and we have
established our identity in international conventions. Around 90 recycling plants located in Alang, Gujarat have
already
received the TEST compliance certificate.
More from Europe and Japan.
Efforts will be made to bring ships to India. The total
cycling capacity of NDTV, which is approximately 4.5 million tonnes
displacement, will be
doubled by 2014. This is
expected to create 1.5 lakh more jobs for our youth.
Our government has maintained fuel supply across the
country even during the long lockdown period through natural gas and petroleum. In
view of the extremely critical situation in the lives of the people, the following major
steps are being announced: The
gas alarms of the First World War and the impact on 8 crore
families will be strengthened to such an extent
that 1 crore more Indians can be covered.
More districts will be covered under the city gas distribution
network in the next three years. A gas pipeline project will be started in the Jammu and Kashmir region. An
Independent Transport System Operator has been
formed to
facilitate
and coordinate the booking of common carrier capacity of all natural gas pipelines on the basis of open access without any discrimination.
Financial Capital We Tweet 1992 Deposit
React 1996  It is my proposal to create a rational single securities market body by integrating the provisions of the Securities Contract
Regulation Act, 1950 and the Government
Securities Act, 2007. The
Government is ready to extend its support to
develop a world-class institutional framework to build confidence among
corporate bond market participants in times of stress
and to enhance secondary market liquidity in general.
This proposed body will
enable the purchase of greenfield securities in both stressed and soft times and will
help in the development of the bond market.
In the Budget 2018-19, the Government had
announced setting up of a system to boost the
non-conventional energy sector. To
further boost the non-conventional energy sector,
I
propose to infuse additional capital of Rs 1000 crore in the Solar Energy Corporation of India
and Rs
1500 crore in the Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency.  To
promote FDI in the insurance sector, I
propose to amend the Insurance Act, 1938. To do this, the
shareholding in insurance companies can be
increased from 4 per cent to 74 per cent,
and
foreign ownership and control can be achieved by adopting safeguards.
Under this new structure, the
majority of investors on the board and
key management personnel will be Indian. At
least 50% of the directors will be independent directors,
and a specified percentage of profits will be
reserved.
Stressed
assets can be resolved by setting up a new structure so that public sector
banks can make higher provisions for their stressed assets. This
requires measures to ensure the recovery of the bank's assets.
An Asset
Reconstruction Company Limited and an Asset
Management Company will be formed to
devolve the existing stressed assets
and take them over.
The assets can then be
disposed of in alternative investment funds
and given to other capable investors
to realise their ultimate value.
Recapitalisation of AP SBs can be done with specific
capacity to spend more time.
Year-2001 This bank has a corpus of Rs 20,000 crore
and
is proposed to be capitalized at Rs 500,000 crore. Deposit Insurance The previous government had
given its approval to increase the deposit insurance cover for bank customers from Rs 1 lakh to Rs 5 lakh. We will
bring a proposal in this session to amend the CGST Act, 1968 to
streamline its provisions
so that in case a bank
fails to discharge its obligations permanently, the
depositors of such bank can
easily get their deposits prematurely up to the
limit covered
under the insurance coverage. This will
help those depositors of State Bank
who are currently under stress. To
improve the credit system along with protecting the interests of small borrowers and
for the bank whose minimum
asset can be up to Rs 100,000, regular
Reconstruction and Reconstruction and Financial
Advice (Enforcement of Activities) Act,
2002.  It is
proposed to reduce the minimum eligible loan limit from the current limit of Rs. 50 lakh to Rs. 2,000,000.
Company Matters The process of eliminating
procedural and technical offences under the Companies Act, 2013 has been
completed. Now we propose to take the
next step towards decriminalizing the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008.
Honourable Speaker
Sir, I propose to amend the definition of small business under the Companies Act, 2013 by raising the
minimum threshold for paid-up capital to not more than Rs.
2 crore from Rs. 5,000,000
and the minimum turnover to not
more than Rs. 20 crore from Rs. 2 crore.
This will make it easier for over 2 lakh
companies to meet their compliance
requirements. This will be a comprehensive
measure that will benefit startups and
innovators. Additionally, I
propose to encourage the
incorporation of One Person Companies by allowing PCs.
So that
they can grow without any restriction on paid-up capital and turnover
and they will be
allowed to convert their company into any other type of company at any time. The
housing loan limit for Indian citizens for forming a ToP company, which is 162
days (82 days), should be increased to 120 days
and Non-Resident Indians (NRIs) should be
allowed to set up their own OTCs in India. The
NCERT framework will be strengthened to ensure speedy resolution of disputes. A
shrinking system will be implemented and
alternative arrangements for debt resolution
and special love and support will be implemented for MS Word CMD.
During the coming fiscal year 2020, we will launch Data Analytics in
Artificial Intelligence Machine Learning
driven MCA21 version 3.0.
This version 3.0 will have
elements of back education, C consultant and compliance management. And by the
best investments and specific shell
disinvestments and strategic acquisitions,
despite the hindrance, we will strategically  Work towards disinvestment